iSpring fans welcome to another
iSpring粉丝欢迎来到另一个
installment of spring tips in this
在此安装弹簧提示
installment we're gonna look at the
分期付款，我们将看看
spring boot maven plugin right so we're
Spring Boot Maven插件正确，所以我们
gonna build a new application here just
要在这里建立一个新的应用程序
a demo who cares it doesn't really
一个真正关心它的演示并不是真的
matter what the application is just
不管应用程序是什么
added into the web support I guess and
添加到网络支持中，我猜是
everything else will just leave alone
其他一切都将独自离开
because we're not gonna forward you so
因为我们不会转发你
much and spring itself as we are gonna
充满活力，如我们所愿
on the on the plugin that we're gonna
在我们要使用的插件上
use to build it so let's open up our
用于构建它，所以让我们打开我们的
terminal and then open up the
终端，然后打开
application here we are
应用这里我们
so let's it open up the ID just a
所以让我们打开ID
regular maven built I could have chosen
我本来可以选择的常规行家
Gradle and the same things apply in the
摇篮和相同的事物适用于
Gradle world but I'll leave that to you
摇篮世界，但我会留给你
is a you know an exercise and
是你知道的运动吗
documentation research to sort of see
文档研究有点像
the analogs both all the things that we
类似物我们所有的东西
can talk about here apply equally though
可以在这里谈论同样适用
so we have the simple application and
所以我们有简单的应用程序
again it doesn't really matter the
同样，这并不重要
application itself doesn't actually
应用程序本身并不实际
matter we can create a rest controller
我们可以创建一个休息控制器
for example and just say get mapping hi
例如，只说获取映射即可
and string hi return
和字符串嗨返回
hello there so there's my my basic
你好，所以这是我的基本
Springwood application we have a build
我们有一个Springwood应用程序构建
here alright this is a spring boot
好吧，这是一个春季靴子
application it's a jar application the
应用程序是一个jar应用程序
so-called fat jar and the the fat jar
所谓的胖子和胖子
has the spring boot maven plugin and to
有春季启动Maven插件，并
understand and appreciate what this
了解并欣赏这是什么
maven plugin does we should remove it
Maven插件我们应该删除它吗
first right so let go here and CD
第一个权利，所以让我们在这里和CD
downloads demo maven clean install
下载演示maven全新安装
package even doesn't matter
包装甚至都没关系
and we get compiled code to go to the
然后我们得到了编译后的代码
target directory there we are if we look
如果我们看目标目录
at the demo jar it's 12 kilobytes but I
在演示jar上是12 KB，但是我
can't run it right it doesn't have a
不能正确运行它没有
meta in Factory and it doesn't have a
元在工厂，它没有一个
manifest file inside that meta entry and
该meta条目内的清单文件，以及
that manifest will tell the JVM what
该清单将告诉JVM什么
class to run what is the main class the
上课主要是什么
class that has the public static void
具有公共静态无效性的类
main method with that information the
具有该信息的主要方法
JVM can then run the code and you know
JVM然后可以运行代码，您知道
start our application without that it's
没有它就启动我们的应用程序
just a jar full of code that could be
只是一个罐子里充满了可能是
loaded in as a library into some other
作为库加载到其他库中
JVM process but that does not end of
JVM进程，但并没有结束
itself constitute a runnable jar you
本身构成一个可运行的罐子
could run this if you specify a main
如果您指定主
class it manually as well right that's
手动对其进行分类也是
an option but you also have to specify
一个选项，但您还必须指定
the class path now the class path here
现在的班级路径这里的班级路径
is nowhere to be found I mean this whole
无处可寻我是说整个
target directory is 260 16 kilobytes but
目标目录是260 16 KB，但是
of course you know I've got embedded
当然，您知道我已经嵌入
I've got Tomcat I've got spring boot
我有Tomcat我有春季靴子
start a web which brings in Tomcat which
启动一个引入Tomcat的网站
we know is at least a you know 10
我们知道至少是你知道10
megabytes right so that's clearly not
兆字节，所以显然不是
everything I need to in the code I can
我可以在代码中执行的所有操作
copy the dependencies here I can use the
在这里复制依赖项，我可以使用
main dependencies plugin maven
主要依赖插件Maven
dependencies copy dip end and C's and is
依赖项复制DIP结尾和C的和是
that right let's see
那个让我们看看
maven depend and see that dependencies
Maven依赖并看到依赖
oh no wonder none of it's working
哦，难怪一切都没有用
hahaha wrong folder let's see all right
哈哈哈错误的文件夹让我们看到所有没事
let's try that
让我们尝试一下
there we go so it was it was mavin
我们去了那真是太难了
dependency copied dependencies and you
依赖性复制了依赖性，您
can see that that has copied all these
可以看到复制了所有这些
different dependencies that I need for
我需要的不同依赖
the application into the target
将应用程序放入目标
directory for / CD target for slash and
/ CD目标的斜杠目录和
then there's a dependency directory and
然后有一个依赖目录
there you can see all the jars required
在那里您可以看到所需的所有罐子
to run this application everything
运行此应用程序的一切
that's inside of it or everything that's
里面的东西或所有的东西
required to make this application work
使此应用程序正常运行所需
right so if I look at this directory
对，所以如果我看这个目录
itself is 18 megabytes there's our
本身是18兆字节
entire thing right and includes the web
整个事情都是正确的，包括网络
support and spinning and logging and all
支持，旋转和记录以及所有
that other stuff right well hibernate
那其他东西很好冬眠
validator yeah so all that is there okay
验证器，是的，所以一切都还好
so we have now a trivial application
所以我们现在有了一个简单的应用程序
well if we wanted to run it we'd have to
好吧，如果我们想运行它，我们必须
specify class path ourselves manually
自己手动指定类路径
Java minus CP and then list all the
Java减去CP，然后列出所有
classes that are rather list all the
列出所有的类
jars in the dependi directory and then
将罐子放在dependi目录中，然后
give it the main main main class to run
给它主要的主要班级
so we're pretty far away from useful
所以我们离有用很远
that's why this maven plugin is so
这就是为什么这个Maven插件是如此
valuable this plugin first of all it it
首先，这个插件很有价值
creates a meta in three and a manifest
在三个和一个清单中创建一个meta
until spring where to find the enable
直到春天在哪里找到启用
code but it actually does a fair bit
代码，但实际上确实可以
more than that you see it actually
比实际看到的更多
embeds all the other jars inside of the
将所有其他罐子嵌入
archive that gets built that's why if I
建立档案，这就是为什么如果我
run this code again may even clean
再次运行此代码甚至可以清除
package there we go there we are
包那里我们去那里我们
CD target I have here another jar and
CD目标我在这里还有另一个罐子，
this jar is 14 Meg's right so that's the
这个罐子是14梅格的右边，那是
compressed version of all the library
所有库的压缩版本
that we looked at before this jar is one
我们在这个罐子之前看过的一个
self-contained thing right it needs only
只需要的独立的东西
a JVM a JRE actually not even at JDI
JVM甚至JDI都没有的JRE
means a JRE and that's it I mean the the
意味着一个JRE，就是我的意思是
the the jar itself is self-contained so
罐子本身是独立的，所以
I can do Java - jar demo snapshot jar
我可以做Java-jar演示快照jar
and that works because of the way that
之所以有效，是因为
the plug-in configure everything let's
插件配置一切，让我们
take a look at the structure of the jar
看一下罐子的结构
to see what I mean so demo ok actually I
明白我的意思，所以演示好吧，我
should have let me see if I
应该让我看看我是否
Nautilus and we'll keep everything
鹦鹉螺，我们将保留一切
except for delete your thing except for
除了删除你的东西外
that there are no we have here Jar xvf
没有我们在这里Jar xvf
demo direct so now if we look at the
演示直接，所以现在，如果我们看一下
directory output here you can see that
目录输出在这里你可以看到
the contents of the jar included boot in
jar中的内容包括启动
meta F and org ignore this jar of course
meta F和org当然会忽略这个罐子
because that's the original jar itself
因为那是原始的罐子本身
org if we look at the tree here org is
org，如果我们看这棵树，org是
the org are in org spring framework boot
组织在组织春季框架启动
loader archive these are actual Java
loader存档，这些都是实际的Java
classes that get put in the root of our
放在我们根源的类
charms just like our normal compiled
像我们正常编译的魅力
code would be had we not had the spring
如果没有春天，代码就可以了
boot maven plugin so this is the code
启动Maven插件，所以这是代码
that the JVM is gonna actually run right
JVM实际上会正确运行
and this is in the right right position
这是正确的正确位置
it's right it's in the right place for
是的，在正确的地方
the G of them to find it and load it
他们中的G找到并加载它
normally and this code actually provides
通常，此代码实际上提供了
its own sort of class traffic provides
它自己的类流量提供
its own class loader and its own idea of
它自己的类加载器和自己的想法
a jar file you can you can see here we
一个jar文件，您可以在这里看到我们
have actually classes called a jar file
实际上有一个称为jar文件的类
this jar file class extends from the
这个jar文件类从
Java util jar jar file class it is a
Java util jar jar文件类
drop-in replacement for that jar class
该jar类的直接替换
which is nice by the way because it
顺便说一句，这很好，因为它
means that tooling can use this
意味着工具可以使用此
mechanism if they want and it'll still
机制，如果他们想要，它仍然会
work right but all this to say this code
工作正常，但所有这些都可以说这段代码
describes a custom class loader and a
描述了自定义类加载器和
custom scheme for working with jars and
使用罐子和
that scheme supports nested jars you see
该方案支持您看到的嵌套罐子
here that we have in the buti'm
在这里，我们在buti'm
directory we have the classes of our
目录中有我们的类
actual application itself the code that
实际应用程序本身的代码
we wrote you know my little rest
我们写信给你知道我的小憩
controller with hi and then the class
控制器，然后喜
path that supports that so this is the
支持的路径，所以这是
stuff that we'd have if we didn't you
如果没有你我们会拥有的东西
know if we weren't using maven plug-in
知道我们是否没有使用Maven插件
this stuff would be at the root this
这些东西将是根源
this Lib directory under the end
这个Lib目录在末尾
wouldn't be there right this Lib
不会在那里，这个库
directory is all the class path it's the
目录是所有的类路径
stuff that we saw in the dependency
我们在依赖项中看到的东西
directory earlier when I ran that maven
我运行那个Maven之前的目录
dependency copy dependencies command
依赖项复制依赖项命令
this is the class path required to
这是所需的类路径
support the application this is the
支持应用程序这是
application itself and
应用程序本身以及
and back in the org directory are this
然后回到org目录中
describes a hierarchy of code is
描述代码的层次结构是
designed to support loading and
设计用于支持加载和
resolving and running the application
解决并运行应用程序
with within the buti'm directory so it's
在buti'm目录中，因此
a it's a fairly different scheme than
这是一个与之完全不同的方案
one you may be used to you may have seen
一个你可能习惯了，你可能已经看到
other things that attempt to get you the
其他企图让您
same effect right there's the uber
同样的效果，还有超级
plug-in and the shade plug-in uber Java
插件和阴影插件uber Java
plug-in in this way the shade plugin
以这种方式插入阴影插件
these are different maven plugins out
这些是不同的Maven插件
there that attempt to give you
那里试图给你
self-contained jars and they're all very
独立的罐子，它们都非常
interesting but most of them we have
有趣，但其中大多数我们都有
found they try and explode the jars into
发现他们试图将罐子炸成
one global namespace and that you know
一个全局名称空间，您知道
you're quickly run into a situation
您很快就会遇到情况
where you have conflicts right the the
你有冲突的地方
jars themselves they the contents of the
自己震撼他们的内容
jars are exploded into a global
罐子爆炸成一个整体
namespace and then so you get conflicts
命名空间，然后发生冲突
and you need to reconcile those
你需要调和那些
conflicts and that gets tedious right
冲突，这很乏味
you get you have things like the meta
你得到像元这样的东西
infrastructure where of course you know
基础设施您当然知道
every jar is gonna have one of those and
每个罐子都会有一个
some constants in there or just they
那里有一些常数，或者只是它们
could and you have to reconcile you have
可以，你必须调和
to reconcile the difference there so
调和那里的差异
that gets tedious very quickly and so we
很快就会变得乏味，所以我们
found that you know wasn't so hard to
发现您知道并不难
support doing it this way to actually
支持以此方式进行实际操作
support resolution of code within a jar
支持jar中的代码解析
as we are here and that's where that
因为我们在这里，那就是那里
whole custom scheme does the only
整个定制方案唯一
limitation to our custom scheme here is
我们的自定义方案的限制是
that if you're writing code that uses
如果您正在编写使用
the system class loader that's not gonna
不会的系统类加载器
work the way you expect it to work
以您期望的方式工作
instead you should be using the context
相反，您应该使用上下文
class loader right so if you are writing
类加载器正确，所以如果您正在编写
code that uses the class loader and you
使用类加载器的代码
know about the class loader then you'll
了解类加载器，那么您将
know what that means if you don't then
知道那不意味着什么
great you're probably fine right you're
太好了，你可能没事吧
not gonna need to worry about it most
不用最担心
libraries most frameworks use the
大多数框架使用的库
context class loader anyway so this is
上下文类加载器，所以这是
not a not a problem that you run into
这不是您遇到的问题
except in very exceptional circumstances
除了非常特殊的情况
but other than that this will work right
但除此之外，这将正常工作
this is actually a self-contained jar
这实际上是一个独立的罐子
this star is not something you want to
这颗星星不是你想要的
put on the class path of other jars
放在其他罐子的类路径上
though of other applications it you know
尽管您知道其他应用程序
you by building it in this way you make
通过以这种方式构建它，您可以
it harder for the JVM to load it
JVM很难加载它
the library doesn't work they do the way
图书馆无法正常工作
you'd expect but that's fine
您会期望的，但这很好
we're trying to build an application not
我们试图构建一个应用程序不是
as self-contained library so we have
作为独立的图书馆，所以我们有
everything within the application and
应用程序中的所有内容，以及
that's fine you know the applications
您知道应用程序就可以了
now like you said we we can we can do
现在就像你说的，我们可以做到
job - jar demo dot snapshot jar we can
工作-jar演示点快照jar我们可以
override properties for example the port
覆盖属性，例如端口
I could say export server port dossier
我可以说出口服务器端口档案
export server underscore port equals
导出服务器下划线端口等于
8020 and then do each other- jar demo
8020，然后互相做一个jar演示
and the application now spins up on port
现在应用程序在端口上旋转
80 20 right so you can see that we're
80 20对，所以您可以看到我们
able to change the default behavior I
能够更改默认行为我
could have a property file here I could
在这里可以有一个属性文件
say echo server the port equals a t10
说回声服务器端口等于t10
application properties and then just you
应用程序属性，然后只有您
know in the same directory and open this
在同一目录中知道并打开它
up again close this one and open that
再次关闭这个并打开那个
one up and you can see here I've got cat
一个，你可以看到这里我有猫
application up properties and I've got
应用程序属性，我已经
the jar so Java - jar demo that jar and
Java罐子-罐子演示罐子和
I said I wanted to run to port 80 10 and
我说我想跑到80 80端口
that puppy file and there we are so I'm
那个小狗文件，我们在那里，所以我
able to change the default behavior of
能够更改的默认行为
the application I'm able to build the
我能够构建的应用程序
self-contained application all I need to
我需要的独立应用程序
do is manage starting and stopping and
要做的是管理启动和停止，
restarting and status in the application
重新启动并在应用程序中显示状态
I need to tail the logs and so on so one
我需要拖尾原木等等
of the common reasons that people use
人们使用的常见原因
application servers like Tomcat right
像Tomcat这样的应用服务器
which is the most obliquity by far an
这是迄今为止最倾斜的
application server in the java community
Java社区中的应用程序服务器
and ecosystem the more the reasons that
和生态系统的原因更多
people use it is because they want to
人们使用它是因为他们想要
have the lifecycle management right the
拥有生命周期管理权
life cycle of the application itself to
应用程序本身的生命周期
start the stop the log following etc so
开始停止下面的日志等
you have to reinvent that in this case
在这种情况下，您必须重新发明
in this case right is so far we don't
在这种情况下，到目前为止我们还没有
have most of that capability and
具有大部分功能，
additionally there's no easy way to
此外，没有简单的方法
manage this you have to have to do that
处理这个，你必须要做
you have to do the admittedly not so
你必须做的当然不是
painful but still tedious work of
痛苦但乏味的工作
installing this as a service in your
将其作为服务安装在您的
operating system if you're running this
操作系统（如果正在运行）
in a production environment
在生产环境中
it's more than likely gonna be some sort
它很有可能会成为某种形式
of UNIX flavor so a Linux and so you're
是UNIX风格的，所以是Linux，所以您
gonna want to install this as a service
想要将其安装为服务
so that it gets run when the application
这样当应用程序运行时
weathering that when the environment
当环境风化
starts up and it's gonna be it's gonna
启动，它将成为
be destroyed when the environment is
当环境
itself destroyed so all of it is a kind
本身就被摧毁了，所以全部都是一种
of left as an exercise for the reader
作为读者的练习
and that's you're using an application
那就是您正在使用的应用程序
server that said we're not using an
表示我们没有使用服务器的服务器
application server we have the embedded
嵌入式应用服务器
web server so we need to solve that
网络服务器，所以我们需要解决
problem ourselves and that's easy to do
问题自己，这很容易做到
with the spin boot configuration here so
在这里使用旋转启动配置
there's a lot of configuration options
有很多配置选项
here for the spring boot maven plugin
这里是Spring Boot Maven插件
right you can specify things like what
正确的，您可以指定诸如
Java agents you want to run which custom
您要运行哪个Java代理自定义
classes directory you want to run you
您要运行的classes目录
know what artifacts you want to include
知道要包括哪些工件
or exclude do you want to specify JMX
或排除您要指定JMX
crit in you know you don't sort of
暴击你知道你不会
specify gem X properties the you know
指定您知道的宝石X属性
lots of different things you can do here
您可以在这里做很多不同的事情
in the maven plugin for the spring boot
在春季启动的Maven插件中
plugin but for what we care about is
插件，但我们关心的是
whether the jar is executive or not so
罐子是否执行
we're gonna make it executive or equals
我们将使其具有执行力或同等水平
true by default it's a executive jar but
默认情况下为true，这是一个执行器，但
that's not quite the same thing as what
那跟什么不太一样
we're talking right here it's a what
我们在说这是什么
we're building now is a a a new kind of
我们正在建造的是一种新的
executive jar so maven clean Anne's main
行政罐，所以行家清洁安妮的主要
clean package
清洁包装
all right mmm seedy target now same
好吧，MMM种子目标现在相同
thing as before basically 14 Meg's but
基本上像以前的14兆，但
this is different
这是不同的
right so less so what I just did is I
没那么对，所以我刚做的就是
did less demo zero one snapshot jar and
较少的演示零一个快照jar和
I'm greeted with a shell script and the
我遇到了一个shell脚本，
shell script is actually the first it's
shell脚本实际上是第一个
the header if it's the first part of the
标头，如果它是第一部分
of the jar archive and the the header
jar档案和标头的内容
the the the shell script does a lot of
shell脚本做了很多
things for you it actually does a lot of
对您而言，它实际上做了很多事情
stuff for you and um it installs a PID
东西给你，它会安装一个PID
directory you know it installs a folder
您知道安装目录的目录
to store a paid file where you can see
将付费文件存储在您可以看到的地方
the status of the application it gets a
应用程序的状态
folder it you know it manages logs it
您知道它管理的文件夹将其记录
manages permissions for the application
管理应用程序的权限
itself it gives you functions that you
它本身给你的功能，你
can use to see if the application is
可以用来查看应用程序是否
running you can say P it you know it's
运行你可以说P你知道它是
running for example you can you know
例如运行，你知道吗
there's a lot of support here I don't
这里没有很多支持
expect you to read all of this yourself
希望你自己阅读所有这些
but suffice it to say there's a lot of
但足以说有很多
functionality for starting and stopping
启动和停止功能
and status seeing and for stopping and
和状态查看以及停止和
force reloading and running the
强制重新加载并运行
application you can see all that here as
应用程序，您可以在此处看到所有内容
commands right so these commands are all
命令正确，所以这些命令都是
supported they're very useful and the
支持他们非常有用，
reason they're useful is because you can
他们有用的原因是因为您可以
use these in conjunction with an ad or
将它们与广告结合使用或
system you know V style initialization
您知道的系统V风格初始化
so the script is meant the script the
因此，脚本是指脚本
the script is actually run before the
该脚本实际上在
JVM runs the jar with this what the
JVM以此来运行jar
script does is it actually loads the jar
脚本确实是它实际上加载了罐子
itself right this coat this the script
本身对这件外套这本剧本
gets run by the operating system it then
然后由操作系统运行
loads itself it reads its own file and
加载自身，它读取自己的文件并
loads the jar and the jar of course is
加载罐子，罐子当然是
the binary data that you see here as
您在此处看到的二进制数据
gobbledygook on my screen is all the
我屏幕上的gobbledygook就是全部
contents of the jar kind of encoded in
罐子中的内容编码为
that and that shell script and to
那和那个shell脚本和
understand how that works you have to
了解你如何工作
consider how the operating system reads
考虑操作系统如何读取
files right the operating system reads
操作系统读取的文件权限
of a program
程序的
the memory starting from the top and
内存从顶部开始
going to the EOF the end of file marker
转到EOF文件结尾标记
right and that's just sort of how most
对，那只是大多数
UNIX operating systems work the JVM
UNIX操作系统可运行JVM
contrary to the operating system weeds
与操作系统杂草相反
it's our archives and applications and
这是我们的档案和应用程序，
reverse it reads from the end of the
反转它从末尾读取
archive until the beginning of file
存档直到文件开始
marker well of course there's no reason
当然，没有理由
that those two things have to agree
那两件事必须达成共识
there's no reason at the beginning of
在开始的时候没有理由
the file for the operating system has to
操作系统文件必须
line up with the beginning of the
与开始处对齐
archive for the JVM in fact you can do
实际上，您可以为JVM存档
some very interesting things if you keep
如果你保持一些非常有趣的事情
those things separate that's what we're
这些东西分开，这就是我们
doing here our shell script has an
在这里，我们的shell脚本有一个
end-of-file marker which the operating
文件结束标记
system then reads and the shell script
系统然后读取和shell脚本
then reads itself and gives it you know
然后读自己，给你你知道的
it gives its own contents to the JVM it
它将自己的内容提供给JVM
does so by reading from the end of the
通过从末尾阅读来做到这一点
shell script which is the jar to the
外壳脚本
beginning of the file marker which is
文件标记的开头是
that of course you know right after the
你当然知道
shell script it's the first byte right
Shell脚本，它是第一个字节
after the shell script it's you know
在shell脚本之后，你知道
there's a discrepancy there but that
那里有差异，但是
works now the benefit of this is of
现在工作的好处是
course I can do this demo all right I
我当然可以做这个演示
didn't have to say Java - char
不必说Java-char
I just executed the program like an
我只是像
executive shell script on my operating
执行shell脚本对我的操作
system I still need a JVM mind you but I
系统我仍然需要一个JVM，但我
just I have that ability already and I
只是我已经具备了这种能力，而我
can now use this within knit D and
现在可以在编织D和
system D so a nip T spring boot maven
系统D，所以是一个压区T
plugin
插入
okay so you say exactly what it goes
好吧，所以你说的确切
true here's a calming little Gradle
是的，这是一个平静的小摇篮
configuration and you can now use this
配置，您现在可以使用此
with an ad or system genie right here so
广告或系统精灵就在这里
you they go sudo LLNS my jar and it said
你他们去须藤LLNS我的罐子，它说
it cetera and it D my app and then once
它等我的应用程序，然后一次
that's done you can say service my apps
这样就可以说服务我的应用程序了
start for example so you get to you get
例如开始，这样你就可以得到
the ability to manage the application as
以以下方式管理应用程序的能力
a service on the operating system just
操作系统上的服务
like my sequel or any other thing that
像我的续集或其他任何东西
you're running as a daemon in the
您正在作为守护程序运行
background and of course you have logs
背景，当然还有日志
written to var log app name
写入var日志应用名称
and there's actually a paid that gets
而且实际上有一种报酬
managed for you by the operating system
由操作系统为您管理
by the script itself as well and you can
脚本本身也可以
tell the operating system to started
告诉操作系统启动
automatically using update our CD my up
自动使用更新我们的CD
default priority etcetera right so you
默认优先级等，所以你
know lots of things you can do here you
你知道很多事情可以在这里做
can also look at the documentation for
也可以查看文档
information on how to secure it right so
有关如何正确保护它的信息
that a it only when it runs in a secure
仅当它在安全的环境中运行时
protective process and with a certain
保护过程并具有一定的
you know protective permissions a lot of
您知道很多保护权限
options right so I could you to prove
选项正确，所以我可以证明
that at your own measure one thing I
你自己衡量的一件事我
want to really mmm you know make sure in
真的想知道你要确保
the sense that you can change everything
可以改变一切的感觉
right
对
including the shell script itself you
包括shell脚本本身
can provide your own custom shell script
可以提供您自己的自定义外壳脚本
and you can even copy ours and just you
你甚至可以复制我们的，只有你
know change it a little bit you can
知道可以稍微改变一下
provide a custom shell script here and
在此处提供自定义的shell脚本，然后
provide your own embedded lunch script
提供您自己的嵌入式午餐脚本
and that long script can do whatever you
那个长脚本可以做什么你
want now maybe you you want to override
现在想要，也许您想覆盖
just the properties that are used inside
只是内部使用的属性
of our large script that's fine as well
我们的大型脚本也很好
you can do that here so a lot of options
你可以在这里做很多选择
I encourage you to prove that and to
我鼓励您证明这一点并
sort of explore that later on but for
稍后进行探索，但对于
our purposes I think that's a good
我们的目的，我认为这是一个好习惯
enough introduction the nice thing about
足够的介绍关于
this char is that it's self-contained I
这个字符是它是独立的我
as I say it's a it's a self-contained
正如我所说的，这是一个独立的
demo application and we have we have got
演示应用程序，我们有
one endpoint here we have one rest
我们这里有一个终点
controller we have three lines of code
控制器，我们有三行代码
and that three lines of code required
那需要三行代码
eighteen megabytes in space might seem a
太空中的18兆字节似乎
little disproportionate but you do get
有点不相称，但你确实
benefits as we've just seen you get
我们刚刚看到的好处
operational benefits from having to
由于
it is co-locate all the libraries in the
它位于所有库中
application archive the binary itself
应用程序归档二进制文件本身
that said things could be more compact I
那说事情可能会更紧凑
agree they could be a little more svelte
同意他们可能会更苗条
a little bit more convenient and this is
有点方便，这是
only a problem if you start archiving
如果您开始存档只是一个问题
these these binaries and something like
这些这些二进制文件和类似的东西
like your Nexus repository artifactory
像您的Nexus存储库工件
there you might not want to store 18
您可能不想在那里存储18
megabytes every single time right this
每一次兆字节就这样
is just a trivial application I haven't
只是一个微不足道的应用程序
even begun to add anything else to it so
甚至开始添加其他东西，所以
in this case you might enjoy the fact
在这种情况下，您可能会喜欢
that you can use the thin launcher now
您可以立即使用瘦启动器
the thin mantra is a custom maven it's a
薄咒是一个定制的专家
custom spring boot maven plugin layout
自定义spring boot maven插件布局
layout is an extension plane for the
布局是用于
spring boot maven plug-in that you can
Spring Boot Maven插件，您可以
override and there's a few default
覆盖，并且有一些默认值
layouts this jar there's dot wire and
布置这个罐子的点线和
then there's a new one that the good
然后有一个新的
doctor sire who is the co-founder of
父亲是谁的联合创始人
both spring boot and spring cloud has
弹簧靴和弹簧云都有
created this is called the spring boot
创建了这个叫做弹簧靴
thin launcher it's a you know not
薄启动器，它是一个你不知道的
officially part of spring boot itself
春季靴本身的正式一部分
but it's very very useful already and
但这已经非常有用了，
you can find the cohere desire spring
你会发现春天的渴望
boot thin mantra the code is fairly
启动瘦咒的代码是相当
simple to get going so here we're gonna
很容易上手，所以在这里我们要
win it we're gonna override the spring
赢了，我们将超越春天
boot plugin here we're gonna add this
启动插件在这里，我们要添加这个
bit here to our spring boot plugin okay
到这里来启动我们的Spring Boot插件
oops don't need this and
哎呀不需要这个
don't need that and we need the version
不需要那个，我们需要版本
it's one not oh six I think yeah 1.6
是一个不是哦，六个，我想是的1.6
release so they're back there's a custom
发布，所以他们回来了，有一个自定义
version and our custom maven plugin with
版本和我们的自定义Maven插件
its own custom spring boots in layout
自己的自定义春季靴子的布局
right but then layout has everything we
是的，但是布局具有我们的一切
need to to run the application but with
需要运行应用程序但
the thin boot layout does it actually it
瘦启动布局确实做到了
installs in the in the binary the
安装在二进制文件中
ability to resolve its own class path
解决自己的上课道路的能力
using maven using a you know the same
使用Maven使用你知道相同
maven dependency management mechanism so
Maven的依赖管理机制
here maven clean package CD target do
这里的Maven清洁包CD目标吗
you - HS demo oops what did i do there
您-HS演示糟糕，我在那里做了什么
do you mind chase okay 20 kilobytes
你介意追逐好吗20 KB
right so it's a little larger than we
对，所以比我们大一点
saw in the very first time when we had
在我们第一次有看到
no plugin at all but it's still
完全没有插件，但仍然
trivially small and if we run this
很小，如果我们运行这个
application everything will still work
应用程序仍然可以正常工作
so Java - jarred demo of snapshot jar
所以Java-快照jar的jarred演示
there we are you can see it's you know
我们在那里，你可以看到它，你知道
the application spun up as quickly as
该应用程序尽快启动
we'd expect except that it's resolving
我们期望除了它正在解决
its class path dynamically if right now
它的类路径（如果现在）是动态的
right now it's looking in the local em -
现在它正在寻找当地的新兴市场-
you know my local m2 repository
你知道我当地的M2仓库
directory and it's finding all the
目录，并找到所有
libraries that are in that that
在那个图书馆
repository directory and it's you know
仓库目录，这是你知道的
loading those as it needs to dynamically
根据需要动态加载
I can tell it to load those dependencies
我可以告诉它加载那些依赖
in a separate class packed I can say job
在一个单独的班级里我可以说工作
up - thin dot root is it I think and
向上-细点根是我认为的
it'll just be right Lib Lib I'm gonna
没错，我要
say yeah drop my star
说是的，放下我的星星
thin Dutch I think it's been that route
瘦小的荷兰人，我认为那是那条路
I say that is CV Lib you can see that
我说那是简历库，你可以看到
when I said thin that root equals Lib it
当我说稀薄等于根的时候
created a directory called Lib there in
在其中创建了一个名为Lib的目录
the repository directory we see that it
我们看到它的存储库目录
has created a class path it has created
已经创建了它创建的类路径
a maven repository basically that has
一个基本上有
all the artifacts needed to run this
运行此程序所需的所有工件
application so it used the maven
应用程序，所以它使用了行家
dependency resolution mechanism when it
依赖解析机制
started up the application and it
启动了应用程序
resolved all the dependencies and put it
解决所有依赖项并将其放入
in that jar now of course if I run the
当然，如果我运行
same command again you know with that
你再次知道相同的命令
same exact invocation it won't need to
完全相同的调用，它不需要
resolve them right there cached right
解决它们就在那里缓存正确
that's what it happened the very first
那就是最初发生的事情
time it ran this I ran that command
它运行的时间，我运行了该命令
relative to the local m2 a repository
相对于本地m2存储库
directory and then it just worked right
目录，然后它正常工作
so here I'm saying that root equals Lib
所以我在说根等于Lib
job - jar demo done whatever Oh see you
工作-jar演示完成了一切，哦，见到你
target okay so again doesn't have to
目标好吧，所以不必再次
resolve anything now consider an
解决任何问题，现在考虑
operating system where you have no
您没有的操作系​​统
dependencies in the on the class path
类路径上的依赖项
you have nothing on the local machine
你在本地机器上什么都没有
nothing on local m2 nothing anywhere
本地m2上没有任何内容
right then you would need to have
那时你需要
internet connection right so the unit
互联网连接正确，所以本机
you need to download it right obviously
您显然需要正确下载
this is not going to work without its
没有它，这是行不通的
dependencies so that adds to the startup
依赖性，从而增加了启动时间
time hopefully you've got fast download
希望你时间很快
capabilities no doubt you do in a
功能无疑是您在
production data center but that's a cost
生产数据中心，但这是一个成本
that you have to be prepared to pay so
你必须准备支付
you can either have it pre cached you
您可以预先将其缓存
can actually stage your your usage of
实际上可以分阶段使用
the libraries the dependencies you can
库，您可以依赖
actually run a pre-flight if you will in
如果您愿意的话，请实际进行预检
which case you can get all the libraries
在这种情况下，您可以获得所有库
downloaded and then cache them as you
下载，然后将它们缓存为您
would write for example here so Java -
例如在这里写这样的Java-
teeth in that root equals jar our equals
那根牙齿等于罐子等于我们
here and you know like that this will
在这里，你知道那样会
download everything to that that
下载所有内容
directory you could do a dry run by
您可以通过以下目录进行试运行
specifying a property here fin dry run
在此指定属性
equals true and that will actually
等于真实，那实际上
download the dependencies for you and
为您下载依赖项并
not start the code so that you get the
不启动代码，以便您获得
best of both worlds you can download
两全其美，您可以下载
everything and then start the
一切，然后开始
application guaranteeing that it's gonna
应用程序保证它会
work when you do start it right and the
当您正确启动它时就可以工作
benefit of that is that of course you
好处当然是你
can you can have all the defenses you
你能拥有所有的防御能力吗
need to run the application but you
需要运行该应用程序，但是您
don't have to store the built
不必存储内置的
application with all the dependencies
具有所有依赖项的应用程序
included in the artifact or or you know
包含在工件中，或者或者您知道
Nexus repository you can have it only in
Nexus资料库只能在
the container itself that needs it right
需要它的容器本身
and or you could just do everything you
或者你可以做所有的事情
know sort of dynamically you could
动态地知道你可以
choose the thinnest smallest container
选择最薄的最小容器
that you need for your operating system
您的操作系统所需的
and then just deploy the tiny thin jar
然后只用一个小罐子
and let it download the the the
并下载
dependency the classpath that you need
依赖您需要的类路径
for that application that will work just
对于该应用程序将只工作
fine as long as your your platform
只要您的平台很好
whatever technology using for cloud
适用于云的任何技术
computing doesn't have a requirement for
计算不需要
timeouts right hopefully you don't need
超时正确，希望您不需要
to long to download all those
渴望下载所有这些
dependencies if you can do it within
依赖，如果你能做到
that time out then great as it happens
那个超时那么好
this trivial spring boot application
这个琐碎的Spring Boot应用程序
that I've just built here is small
我刚建在这里很小
enough that and quick enough that it
足够快
will download and work just fine on
将下载并正常工作
something like cloud foundry
像云铸造厂
right so if I if I were to push the
对，所以如果我要推动
application here with it as you can see
您可以看到这里的应用程序
here CF push might be my my app minus P
在这里CF Push可能是我的应用减去P
target demo jar and then to specify a
目标演示jar，然后指定一个
build pack this will actually stage the
构建包，这实际上将上演
jars before the applications tries to
在应用程序尝试执行之前先进行jar
start up so it's a it inserts itself
启动，所以它是一个插入自身
into phase in the cloud for any life
终生融入云端
stuck on the cloud for the app lifecycle
在应用生命周期内停留在云中
before the application starts up I
在应用程序启动之前
downloads all the jars and then it does
下载所有罐子，然后执行
job my start and so you're not again
做好我的开始，所以你不再
you're not counting against that that
你不反对那个
time out but even if I were just to do
超时，但是即使我只是要做
CF push my app specifying this jar and
CF推我的应用程序指定此jar和
ignoring the build back you know for for
忽略您知道的构建
this trivial application that would
这个琐碎的应用
absolutely work right it's small enough
绝对正确，它足够小
that I could get that done in the time
我可以在那个时候完成
before the the time that applies right
在适用时间之前
so you can either use a custom build
因此您可以使用自定义版本
pack to get around that or you can just
打包以解决这个问题，或者你可以
you know if it's small enough it'll just
你知道它是否足够小
fit and you might not even have that
适合，你甚至可能没有
problem who knows I mean the point is
谁知道我的意思是问题是
this is a good option and there's very
这是一个不错的选择，
few cases where it's gonna be a problem
少数情况下会出现问题
the only places I can think of where you
我能想到的唯一地方
might have problems is if you're running
可能有问题，如果您正在跑步
against a timeout when you start up
启动时超时
right because it's going to have to do
对，因为这必须要做
all this when the program gets run I
程序运行时所有这些我
want to when it starts up so keep that
想要它何时启动，所以保持
in mind
心里
and you know
而且你知道
I like the thin approach I think it's
我喜欢瘦的方法
like the best of both worlds you can you
就像两全其美一样
can do interesting things too because
也可以做一些有趣的事情，因为
remember the the class path is being
记得上课的路
provided external to the application if
在应用程序外部提供，如果
you wanted to you can actually provide a
您想要的实际上可以提供
thinned up properties file that then
细化属性文件，然后
contains its own dependency manifest
包含自己的依赖清单
right that's actually what's happening
正确，这实际上是正在发生的事情
here if you look at this char let me see
在这里，如果你看这个字符，让我看看
you open this again
你再打开一次
and I will grab only that delete that
我只会抓住那个删除的那个
I'll say unzip there you go see if you
我会说解压缩你去看看你
look at the directory here you can see
看这里的目录你可以看到
the directory contains the Menem code it
该目录包含Menem代码
contains a thin jar wrapper class which
包含一个薄罐包装类
in turn is tailgating to this dim
反过来正在使这种昏暗
application and to your maven pom it's
应用程序和您的Maven Pom
using the maven pom that's in the
使用中的Maven Pom
archive to resolve the dependencies but
存档以解决依赖关系，但
you can provide those dependencies in a
您可以在
custom format as well you can provide
您也可以提供自定义格式
your custom preppy file so thin dot
您的自定义预科文件太薄了
properties right so here it says
属性正确，所以在这里说
dependencies spring boots starter web
依赖项Spring Boots Starter Web
equals org spring framework boot spring
等于org spring框架boot spring
boot start a web right so here's yeah
引导正确地启动网站，这是
you an externalized cut you know custom
你是一个外在的削减，你知道习惯
dependencies and you can use that as the
依赖关系，您可以将其用作
class path you could overwrite the class
您可以覆盖课程的课程路径
path that the the application has inside
应用程序内部的路径
of it so if you want to upgrade spring
因此，如果您想升级弹簧
mood and spring cloud but nothing else
心情和春天的云，但没有别的
you know you want to change the
你知道你想改变
dependency version for example um you
依赖版本，例如um you
could do that by overriding the bomb's
可以通过取代炸弹来做到这一点
section in our property so here you'd
部分，所以在这里
say BMS that's the spring boot maven
说BMS是春季启动专家
bombs a bill of material dependencies
炸毁物料依赖清单
bombs that spring boot dependencies
弹簧启动依赖的炸弹
equals Oryx bring free mcboot spring
等于Oryx带来了免费的mcboot spring
boot dependencies 1.5 times 6 really so
启动依赖项1.5乘以6确实如此
here it would be forcibly upgrading the
在这里，它将被强制升级
awareness of a particular penalty 21.5
意识到特殊处罚21.5
dot six everything that uses the spring
点六点用弹簧的一切
boot bomb would which in a spring wood
靴子炸弹会在春天的木头
application is everything would now be
应用程序就是现在的一切
pinned to win dot 5.6 you don't have to
别着急赢得5.6点
recompile the code now do I recommend
现在我建议重新编译代码
doing this in production code no of
在生产代码中执行此操作
course not I mean you should definitely
当然不是我意思是你绝对应该
absolutely go through the regression
绝对经历回归
test and auditing and all this stuff but
测试和审核以及所有这些东西
it can be very convenient in a pinch if
如果紧要的话，这可能非常方便
you need to do that and you know you can
您需要这样做，并且您知道可以
we try our best to keep things saying so
我们尽力使事情如此
that they work backwards and backwards
他们来来回回地工作
and forward compatible you know
并转发兼容，你知道
obviously we don't
显然我们不
this with a a giant you know 1.56 to
这与一个巨人，你知道1.56
23.0 you know bump or something like
23.0你知道颠簸之类的东西
that but you would you would be what
那，但是你会的
you'd be better off if you knew about
如果你知道的话，你会过得更好
that if you had a security vulnerability
如果您有安全漏洞
that you need to get patched right now
您需要立即修补
something like that right that's just a
诸如此类的权利
convenience so you have a lot of options
方便，所以您有很多选择
here right a lot of options to run your
这里有很多选择来运行您的
Springwood application and again we've
Springwood应用程序，我们再次
talked into I've talked about servlet
谈到我已经谈到了servlet
container options right in previous in a
上一个容器选项
previous spring tip so that's not what
以前的春季小贴士，那不是什么
we're talking about here we're talking
我们正在谈论这里，我们正在谈论
about the spring boot maven plugin and a
关于Spring Boot Maven插件和一个
number of different strategies for
不同策略的数量
running them also of note is that the
运行它们还值得注意的是，
so-called fat jar thing that I showed
我展示的所谓的胖子罐子里的东西
you that can be used with a bar the
您可以与酒吧一起使用
first approach that we showed you with
我们向您展示的第一种方法
the maven plug-in without it being
没有它的Maven插件
executive you can use that with a dot
执行官，你可以用一个点
waar as well that actually gets you the
Waar以及实际上让您
best of both worlds you can deploy that
两全其美，您可以部署
into a server container environment and
进入服务器容器环境
also do java - jar my dot wah right and
也做java-jar我的dot wah正确和
that actually get to UM you know
真正进入UM的过程
something at work in both environments
在两种环境中都起作用的东西
so a lot of options here a lot of
所以这里有很多选择
flexibility now one thing that isn't
灵活性现在不是一件事
there yet that I'd love to see
在那里，我很想看到
especially in light of day are he9 Java
尤其是今天，he9 Java
9 is the ability to have for this
9是为此拥有的能力
for the shell script that we saw earlier
对于我们之前看到的shell脚本
to download a JDK I'm modern GDK and j
下载我是现代GDK和J的JDK
9i I think it's a perfect vehicle for
9i我认为这是
that it provides modularity and that
它提供了模块化，并且
modularity applies mostly to the JVM
模块化主要适用于JVM
itself you can decompose the JVM into
本身，您可以将JVM分解为
smaller modules that you can then
较小的模块，然后您就可以
repackage and whatever range but you
重新包装和任何范围，但你
want and so you could for example build
想要，所以你可以例如建立
a JRE that doesn't have the code for
没有代码的JRE
korba well good you know we weren't
科巴很好，你知道我们不是
applying and using that in later
在以后应用和使用
application so we can cut that out you
应用程序，以便我们可以将其删除
can have a custom redistributable JRE
可以有一个自定义的可再发行JRE
and I think Oracle even signals that
而且我认为Oracle甚至发出信号
they expect applications to to ship the
他们希望应用程序能够将
JVM with their they expect Java 9 the
JVM和他们期望Java 9
job and I'm Jerry to be shipped to the
工作，我是杰里，要运到
application so so as to make it easier
应用程序，以便使其更容易
for developers to get a consistent
为开发人员提供一致的
experience right especially now that
立即体验
they're gonna be releasing a lots of new
他们会发布很多新的
games every every what is it six months
每六个月进行一次游戏
something that they're gonna do schemer
他们要做的事
it's a twice a year something like that
一年两次这样的事情
so it could be very valuable to paint
所以油漆可能很有价值
your application to a particular JVM as
您的应用程序到特定的JVM
opposed to relying on whatever resident
反对依靠任何居民
JVM is on the operating system so we'll
JVM在操作系统上，因此我们将
see and I think that would be a
看到，我认为那将是一个
interesting extension you could do that
有趣的扩展，你可以做到
of course you could already since you
当然可以，因为你
can control the launch script you can
可以控制启动脚本
provide you own Jerry resolution
为您提供自己的杰瑞解决方案
mechanisms we could actually download
我们实际上可以下载的机制
your own as opposed to the Java you know
自己的而不是Java
Java command detection logic that's in
包含的Java命令检测逻辑
their launch script right now so okay so
他们的启动脚本现在就可以了
with that we've looked at the default
这样，我们查看了默认
behavior of spring boot and the maven
弹簧靴和行家的行为
plugin without the maven plugin we get
没有Maven插件的插件，我们得到了
to a jar we looked at how you could
到一个罐子里，我们看着你怎么能
resolve the classpath if you didn't have
如果没有的话，解析类路径
that plug and we looked at the spring
那个插头，我们看着春天
boot maven plugin and saw what the
启动Maven插件，看到了什么
default behavior gets you we looked at
默认行为让您了解我们
some of the configuration options and
一些配置选项和
saw that you can change a good deal of
看到你可以改变很多
things about the the resulting fat jar
关于产生的脂肪罐的事情
using the maven plugin we also looked at
使用maven插件，我们还查看了
the executive all option right in the
高管的所有选择权
executive launch script that you get in
您进入的执行启动脚本
UNIX operating systems and how that
UNIX操作系统以及如何
allows you to run the application in
允许您在以下位置运行应用程序
system D and init.d
系统D和init.d
style environments and then we finally
风格的环境，然后我们终于
looked at the one of many possible
看着许多可能之一
layouts this one is called the thin
这种布局称为薄
layout that applies to the spring boot
适用于弹簧靴的布局
maven plugin this is a project from Dave
maven插件，这是Dave的一个项目
sired dr. Dave sire when I spring team
先生博士当我组队时的戴夫下
members and we then talked about some of
成员，然后我们讨论了一些
these shoes you may have if you use this
如果你用这双鞋的话
approach and some of the virtues you may
方法和您可能拥有的某些美德
have if you use this approach so with
如果您使用这种方法，那么
that thanks so much for watching and
非常感谢您的观看和
we'll see you next time
下次见
you
您